Angelo Poole

New York, New York | 929-290-7228 | angelo.poole@gmail.com

GitHub: Angelo P | Medium | LinkedIn

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Software engineer with customer-facing experience and a background in Biological sciences. Possess strong skills in team building, instructional design, and software development. Interned at Accenture and Google. Experienced in cloud software and algorithm implementation and loves collaboration on large projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby | Rails | SQL | Javascript | React / Redux | Expressis | MongoDB| Node.is

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Sound Visualizer - Github-Front | Github-Back

Allows for the creation of a personalized soundscape based on flowers that you choose

- Deconstructed data coming from sound to create a circular sound visualizer
- Developed backend routes and connections to the frontend

StarBounty - Github

A bounty hunting system developed for watchers of the Mandalorian. Rails Monolith

- Established the models and schema for the project to allow for successful deployment
- Researched and learned necessary materials for the creation of an authentication system

Raycasting - Github

A simple canvas that creates rays and simulates 2d light in Real-time

- Figured out how to pass functions and objects between files
- Researched and learned how to utilize the p5.is library

EXPERIENCE

Uniglo NY, NY Retail Associate

09/2019 - 12/2019

- Met weekly sales goals by providing excellent customer care
- Ensured that customer interactions ended in positive outcomes within a fast-paced environment

Google NY, NY Internship

07/2017 - 09/2017

- Facilitated learning opportunities for young developers through Code Nation
- Designed courses on the origins of code to motivate young developers to begin programming

Accenture NY, NY Internship

07/2016 - 09/2016

- Developed a chatbot that aids customers that interact with salesforce
- Monitored and debugged complex issues with Accenture related technology
- Worked on cloud solutions for Accenture clients

EDUCATION

Flatiron School 12/2019 - 03/2020

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript, computer programming program

Borough of Manhattan Community College, NY, NY

08/ 2019 - 08/2020

Credits toward a Biology degree